Claude proceeds to start processing the written command request.
Claude reads the provided files to assess the current design.
Claude searches for design files and checks for actual location.
Claude searches for relevant files in the project file directory.
Claude reads the design timing demo files and checks status of the files.
Claude finds an error while reading actual constraints for ORFS design.
Claude checks where ORFS is located to resume processing.
The program continues running, displaying errors from previous attempts.
Program checks for OpenROAD scripts, finding them to be available.
Program checks the GCD design, reads design and constraint files.
Program runs baseline flow, sees constraint is too aggressive and checks build results.
The program identifies there are no existing results and tries the baseline flow.
Program identifies a permission issue and tries different approaches.
The program continues and indicates need to run as root to fix.
Program encounters more issues and gives an error as sudo is required.
The program takes a different approach and checks which sessions exist.
The program takes another approach since the original constraint has timing violations.
Program applies an optimized timing constraint.
Program now applies the improved timing constraint for a better result.
User begins to type in a command to optimise WNS.
The system writes new timing constraints and configurations to files.
The system creates a comprehensive test script to test optimizations.
The script tests multiple clock periods and optimizations.
The system writes a WNS optimization script and marks it as executable.
The system is still applying the optimized timing constraints now.
The system writes a quick reference guide for WNS optimization.
The script tests clock periods/config optimizations to find best WNS.
System writes and marks the optimization script as executable now.
The system writes WNS optimization quick reference guides.
The code is writing optimized timing constraints and configuration files.
The code proceeds to create a test script for multiple optimizations.
The program is writing lines in "optimize_WNS_SH" file.
Bash changes the mode of the optimize WNS script file.
Writes to the WNS Optimization Guide a quick reference for the GCD.
The program is now updating the README with optimization strategies.
Now the code is updating the ReadMe comprehensive guide file.
The display shows the manual steps for automated optimization.
The assistant scrolls through code displayed in the text editor.
Code about GCD WNS Optimization and target frequencies is displayed.
It references a reference for GCD/Nangate45 with current status.
Assistant adds new optimization strategy with updated README updates.
A comprehensive test script will test multiple optimization strategies.
The WNS optimization guide is being updated for quick reference guide.
It mentions lack of active counts and different approaches.
Demo already shows that the original constraints has timing violations.
An optimized constraint file contains a number that changes.
Baseline flow now running to assess WNS.
The next step is to identify timing violations and critical paths.